Guide to the Gay Cable Network Archives, 1982-2001 MSS.231
Fales Library and Special Collections
Gay Cable Network Archives
1982-2001
1984-2000
Fales Library and Special Collections
Gay Cable Network
MSS.231
400 Linear Feet (254 Boxes)
Founded in 1982 by Louis P. Maletta, the Gay Cable Network was the premiere media chronicler of events and personalities of the lesbian, gay, bisexual, and transgender (LGBT) community for nearly two decades. GCN programming broadcast on public access television in New York City and other major cities worldwide.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Arrangement
Series I: About Entertainment- Unavailable
Series II: AIDS Memorial Quilt- Unavailable
Series III: Be Our Guest- Unavailable
Series IV: Candied Camera- Unavailable
Series V: Commercials, Trailers, and Miscellaneous Promos- Unavailable
Series VI: Dungeon Knights- Unavailable
Series VII: Emerald City- Unavailable
Series VIII: Events- Unavailable
Series IX: Gay Games and Sporting Events- Unavailable
Series X: Gay USA
Series XI: Health and Fitness with Jessie Garcia- Unavailable
Series XII: Interviews- Unavailable
Series XIII: In the Dungeon- Unavailable
Series XIV: In the Life- Unavailable
Series XV: Lavender Health- Unavailable
Series XVI: LGBT Parades, Marches, and Rallies- Unavailable
Series XVII: Men & Films- Unavailable
Series XVIII: Miscellaneous Programs and Clips- Unavailable
Series XIX: Music Videos- Unavailable
Series XX: Out on Wednesdays- Unavailable
Series XXI: Political Conventions- Unavailable
Series XXII: Pride and Progress / The Right Stuff
Series XXIII: Public Service Announcements- Unavailable
Series XXIV: Sixth Floor Harrison- Unavailable
Series XXV: Sports Scan- Unavailable
Series XXVI: Static- Unavailable
Series XXVII: Stonewall Place After Dark- Unavailable
Series XXVIII: Small Format Video- Unavailable
Series XXIX: Lou Maletta and GCN Files
Oversize Series XXIX: Lou Maletta and GCN Files
Series XXX: Photographs
Series XXXI: Objects
Oversize Series XXXI: Objects
Series XXXII: Lou Maletta Interviews- Unavailable
Scope and Contents
Founded in 1982 by Louis P. Maletta, the Gay Cable Network was the premiere chronicler of major events and personalities of the lesbian, gay, bisexual, and transgender (LGBT) community for nearly two decades. Broadcast on public access television in New York City and other major cities worldwide, GCN covered key LGBT civil rights battles, five presidential conventions, as well as the AIDS pandemic and social protests often marginalized in the mainstream media. On televised programs like Gay USA, Pride and Progress, The Right Stuff, Men and Films, Candied Camera, In the Dungeon, and Lavender Health, GCN conducted numerous interviews with leading politicians, medical and educational professionals, entertainers, and social activists.
Historical Note
Under the direction of Lou Maletta, and broadcast on Manhattan Cable Television Channel 35, Gay Cable Network (GCN) began in 1982 and stopped production in 2001. GCN was the first network in the nation to openly appeal to a gay, lesbian, bisexual, and transgender audience. GCN initially broadcast a series titled "Men in Films," which explored the gay male image in media and male erotica, and the network soon evolved to host a wider variety of content, including news and current affairs programs which covered political developments affecting the LGBT community and the AIDS/HIV epidemic. Throughout its time, GCN provided coverage of the Democratic and Republican National Conventions, with on-floor correspondents interviewing candidates and delegates, as well as coverage of the 1987 and 1993 LGBT rights marches on Washington. A documentary aired on GCN, "Out in the 90's," earned the network a Special Recognition Award at the inaugural GLAAD Media Awards in 1990.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Only Series II, X, XXI, and XXII are accessible for viewing at this time. Some titles remain unavailable due to tape deterioration.
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact Fales Library and Special Collections, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596] with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Louis P. Maletta in 2008. The accession number associated with this gift is 2008.231.
Gays -- Political activity -- New York (State) -- New York.; Video recordings |x Political aspects.; Video recordings -- Social aspects.; Lesbians -- United States; Gays in popular culture.; Cable television; LGBTQ+ activism; Gay men.; Gay liberation movement.; Gay activists -- New York (State) -- New York.; Gay Men's Health Crisis, Inc.; Northrop, Ann; Humm, Andy; Maletta, Louis P.
- Series II: AIDS Memorial Quilt
  Scope and Content
  Titles have been transcribed from original container annotations. These tapes have not been viewed by an archivist.
  - Names Project, August 12, 1987; ID: 231.1630 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1630)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Format: 3/4 in. Umatic
    Duration: Unknown
  - Quilt at the Elipse - Tape Number 1, October 8, 1988; ID: 231.1631A (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1631A)
  - [1]--Quilt at the Elipse - Tape Number 2 [2]--Number 15, October 8, 1988; ID: 231.1632 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1632)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Currently not available for viewing.
  - Candlelight March - Tape Number 3, October 8, 1988; ID: 231.1633 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1633)
  - Candlelight March - Tape Number 4, October 8, 1988; ID: 231.1634 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1634)
  - [1]--Quilt-Lincoln Memorial and B-roll - Tape Number 5 [2]--Gay Cable Network - Number 3, October 8-9, 1988; ID: 231.1635 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1635)
  - The Quilt, Washington D.C., October 8, 1988; ID: 231.1636A (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1636A)
    Format: VHS
  - Dupont Circle - Tape Number 6, October 9, 1988; ID: 231.1637A (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1637A)
  - Dupont Circle - Tape Number 7, October 9, 1988; ID: 231.1638 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1638)
  - [1]--Dupont Circle - Tape Number 8 [2]--Fred, October 9, 1988; October 21, 1991; ID: 231.1639A (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1639A)
  - [1]--B-roll of Capitol Building and Quilt, October 9,1988 [2]--VHS Tape Number 1, Washington D.C., October 8, 1988, ID: 231.1640 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1640)
  - Children's Quilt Project - Tape Number 1, October 10, 1988; ID: 231.1641A (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1641A)
    Format: 3/4" Umatic
  - Washington D.C. B-roll, October 10, 1988; ID: 231.1642A (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1642A)
  - Common Threads: Stories From the Quilt, Part 1 of 2, 1988; ID: 231.1643 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1643)
    Duration: 60 minutes
  - Common Threads: Stories From the Quilt, Part 2 of 2, 1988; ID: 231.1644 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1644)
    Duration: 20 minutes
  - Common Threads: Stories of the Quilt, 1988; ID: 231.1645 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1645)
    Duration: 80 minutes
  - The Names Project, AIDS Quilt Public Service Announcement Number 1, September 16, 1996; ID: 231.1646 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1646)
  - The Names Project, AIDS Quilt Public Service Announcement Number 2, September 16, 1996; ID: 231.1647 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1647)
  - Names Project Public Service Announcement Selection, circa 1985-1999; ID: 231.1648 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1648)
  - [1]--Washington Quilt [2]--Mr. Leather New York, Undated; ID: 231.1649 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1649)
    Program content: David Ranada's Camera
  - Universal Studios Florida, World AIDS Day Candlelight Ceremony and AIDS Memorial Quilt, December 1, 1996; ID: 231.2163 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.2163)
    Duration: 11 minutes
    Program content: B-roll, Dub with AMOL
- Series IV: Candied Camera
  - [1]--Candied Camera [2]--"Les Incroyables" from Beta Nora, [1993]; 231.1135 (Box 73, Cassette 231.1135, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1135)
    Scope and Contents
    Program content: [1]--Nora Burns
    Format: 3/4 in. Umatic, TRT: [00:29:00]
  - Candied Camera, [1993]; 231.1136 (Box 73, Cassette 231.1136, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1136)
    Program content: Music
  - [1]--Candied Camera No. 17 [2]--Candied Camera, 1/19/[1993], 231.1137 (Box 73, Cassette 231.1137, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1137)
    Program content: [1]--England
  - [1]--Candied Camera with Nora Burns No. 14A [2]--Candied Camera, 2/23/[1993], 231.1138 (Box 73, Cassette 231.1138, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1138)
    Program content: [1]--Hawaii
  - [1]--Candied Camera, 3/8/[1993] [2]--Religion, 231.1139 (Box 73, Cassette 231.1139, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1139)
  - [1]--Candied Camera No. 2A [2]--Candied Camera, Wed. 3/10/[1993], 231.1140 (Box 73, Cassette 231.1140)
    Program content: Cabaret
    Format: 3/4 in. Umatic, TRT: 00:29:00. This tape is not transferable. A digital access copy is not available.
  - Candied Camera, 3/15/[1993], 231.1141 (Box 73, Cassette 231.1141, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1141)
    Program content: Southern Sports
    Format: 3/4 in. Umatic, TRT: 00:29:00
  - [1]--Candied Camera No. 9 [2]--Candied Camera, 3/15/[1993], 231.1142 (Box 73, Cassette 231.1142, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1142)
    Program content: [1]--Circle
  - Candied Camera, 3/22/[1993], 231.1143 (Box 73, Cassette 231.1143, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1143)
    Program content: Videos.
  - Candied Camera, 3/29/[1993], 231.1144 (Box 73, Cassette 231.1144, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1144)
    Program content: France
  - [1]--Candied Camera, QMTV, 3/31/1993 [2]--Candied Camera, 5/26, 231.1145 (Box 73, Cassette 231.1145, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1145)
  - [1]--Candied Camera, 4/7/[1993] [2]--Shark Sequence II, 231.1146 (Box 73, Cassette 231.1146, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1146)
    Program content: Outer Space
  - [1]--Candied Camera No. 3A, 3/17/1993 [2]--Candied Camera, 4/13, 231.1147 (Box 73, Cassette 231.1147, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1147)
    Program content: [1]--Funky Divas
  - [1]--Candied Camera No. 6A [2]--Candied Camera, 4/21/[1993], 231.1148 (Box 73, Cassette 231.1148, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1148)
    Program content: [1]--[Container]--Cabaret II [Cassette]--Cabaret with Mark Jacobs
  - [1]--Candied Camera Vol. I No. 17, 5/12/[1993] [2]--Candied Camera No. 5A, 231.1149 (Box 73, Cassette 231.1149, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1149)
    Program content: QTV
  - [1]--Candied Camera, 5/19/[1993] [2]--Candied Camera, 6/2/[1993], 231.1150 (Box 74, Cassette 231.1150, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1150)
    Program content: Beach
  - [1]--Candied Camera No. 9A [2]--Candied Camera, 6/30/[1993], 231.1151 (Box 74, Cassette 231.1151, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1151)
    Program content: [1]--Beach II
  - [1]--Candied Camera, 7/28/1993 [2]--Candied Camera, 1/5, 231.1152 (Box 74, Cassette 231.1152, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1152)
    Format: 3/4 in. Umatic. TRT: 00:29:00
    Program content: [1]--Fag Hag Show
  - [1]--Candied Camera, 8/3/[1993] [2]--Candied Camera No. 12A, 8/93, 231.1153 (Box 74, Cassette 231.1153, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1153)
    Program content: [2]--Dark Summer
  - [1]--Candied Camera, 7/7/[1993] [2]--Candied Camera, 8/4/[1993], 231.1154 (Box 74, Cassette 231.1154, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1154)
    Program content: Misc '94
  - [1]--Candied Camera No. 8A, 8/25/1993 [2]--Candied Camera No. 11A [3]--Candied Camera, 9/29, 10/1, 231.1155 (Box 74, Cassette 231.1155, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1155)
    Program content: [2]--Best Of
  - [1]--Candied Camera [2]--Candied Camera, 9/15/[1993], 231.1156 (Box 74, Cassette 231.1156, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1156)
    Program content: [1]--P-Town Dykes
    General
  - [1]--Candied Camera [2]--Candied Camera, 9/29/[1993], 231.1157 (Box 74, Cassette 231.1157, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1157)
    Program content: [1]--Dear Friends
  - [1]--Candied Camera No. 16 [2]--Candied Camera, 10/6/[1993], 231.1158 (Box 74, Cassette 231.1158, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1158)
    Program content: [1]--Boy Show
  - [1]--Candied Camera No. 17A [2]--Candied Camera, 10/20/[1993], 231.1159 (Box 74, Cassette 231.1159, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1159)
  - [1]--Candied Camera [2]--Candied Camera, 10/27/[1993], 231.1160 (Box 74, Cassette 231.1160, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1160)
    Program content: [After] Dark
  - [1]--Candied Camera No. 17 [2]--Candied Camera, 11/3/[1993], 231.1161 (Box 74, Cassette 231.1161, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1161)
    Program content: [1]--Animals
  - [Container]--[1]--Candied Camera No. 1A [2]--Candied Camera, 11/17/[1993] [Cassette]--[1] Be Our Guest Vol. XI, No. 6 [2]--Candied Camera, 11/17/[1993], 231.1162 (Box 74, Cassette 231.1162, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1162)
    Program content: [Container]--[1]--[Cable] Madness
  - [1]--Candied Camera No. 15A [2]--Candied Camera, 11/24/[1993], 231.1163 (Box 74, Cassette 231.1163, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1163)
    Program content: [1]--Fall Show
  - [1]--Candied Camera, 12/15/[1993] [2]--Gay USA Vol. XII No. 21, ID: 231.1164 (Box 74, Cassette 231.1164, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1164)
  - [1]--Candied Camera No. 20 Rx [2]--Candied Camera, 6/8/1994 [3]--Candied Camera, 7/28 [4]--Candied Camera, 8/25, 231.1165 (Box 74, Cassette 231.1165, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1165)
    Program content: [2]--Doctors and Nurses
- Series X: Gay USA
  Some titles and program content have been transcribed from original container annotations. These tapes have not been viewed by an archivist.
  - 1990 Vol. [VIII]
    - Gay USA No. 2, 1990; ID: 231.0564 (Box 36, Media ID: 231.0564)
      Currently available for viewing.
      Duration: [unknown]
      Program Content: GCN National Show: Parades
    - [1]--Gay USA, Vol. [VIII], Episode No. 2 [Air date: 7/5/1990] [2]--Pride and Progress, July 1990; ID: 231.0098 (Box 7, Media ID: 231.0098)
      Duration: 00:59:00
      Program Content: Parades
    - Gay USA, Vol. [VIII], Episode No. 3 [Air date: 7/12/1990], July 1990; ID: 231.0099 (Box 7, Media ID: 231.0099)
      Program content: Parades
      Program Content: Unknown
    - [1]--Gay USA, Vol. [VIII] Episode No. 4 [Air date: 7/19/1990], July 1990; ID: 231.0100 (Box 7, Media ID: 231.0100)
      COMMERCIAL: OutWeek Magazine
      1. Footage of the International AIDS Conference in San Francisco
      COMMERCIAL: 550-TOOL (8665), ONLY .10 MIN - .20 FIRST MIN
      2. Phil Zwickler, Editor of PWA "Newsline", interviews Peter Staley and Garance Frank-Ruta, of ACTUP New York, regarding the International AIDS Conference in San Francisco.
      COMMERCIAL: Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC), "The Time Is Now…Get the Facts"
      3. Footage of the 13th Anniversary Celebration of MECLA. Includes footage of Christopher McCauley; Sheila James Kuehl, of the So. Calif. Womens Law Center; and Dave Pallone, gay ex-Major League umpire.
      COMMERCIAL: The Monster, NYC club and bar
      4. Footage of the Human Rights Campaign Fund Gala with Joan Rivers
      5. Human Rights Campaign Fund "Washington Update" regarding the Americans with Disabilities Act, which would include individuals with HIV/AIDS. Includes interview with Karen Friedman, lobbyist.
      6. Lou Maletta interviews Robert Brading, Director of the Fund for Human Dignity, regarding a recent staff walk-out. Also includes footage of David Stickle, former staff member of the Fund, discussing the recent staff walk-out.
      7. "Naming Names": Janet Rogers, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD), discusses a recent newspaper article regarding the Gay Officers Action League (GOAL).
      COMMERCIAL: Laser Medical Associates
      8. "Lavender Health": Ron Vachon, Director of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns, interviews Polly Thomas, M.D., Director of the AIDS Surveillance Unit, regarding recent HIV/AIDS-related statistics.
      9. Footage of play "Men of Manhattan".
      COMMERCIAL: Brought to you in part by 550-TOOL (8665), ONLY .10 MIN - .20 FIRST MIN
    - Gay USA, Vol. [VIII], Episode No. 5 [Air date: 7/26/1990], July 1990; ID: 231.0101 (Box 7, Media ID: 231.0101)
      Currently available.
      1. Andy Humm discusses recent general events that relate to the LGBT community.
      2. Footage of Hon. David N. Dinkins, NYC Mayor, at the First Mayor's Conference for Lesbian and Gay Press. Includes footage of Lou Maletta.
      3. Footage of ACTUP protest of President George Bush. Includes footage of Lou Maletta interviewing protest attendees.
      4. Footage of Human Rights Campaign Fund Dinner in Los Angeles. Includes footage of Karen [Ocamb], of GCN Los Angeles, interviewing Midge Costanza, Assistant to President Carter; [Jeannie Wolf, host]; [Tom Gingerella, chairperson]; and Tim McFeeley, Executive Director of the Human Rights Campaign Fund (HRCF).
      5. Footage of Grace Jones performing at the Palladium, to raise money for ACTUP and the Keith Haring Foundation. Includes footage of Lou Maletta interviewing attendee Robert Parker.
      COMMERCIAL: New Millennium Productions presents "Tarzana Queen of the Jungle"
      6. Lou Maletta interviews Marc Huestis, director, regarding his film "Men in Love".
      7. Lou Maletta interviews Shirley [Purvitis], Indianapolis Police Department Liaison, regarding her position and responsibilities.
      8. "Naming Names": Dr. Henry Yeager, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD), discusses recent homophobia in New York Magazine.
      9. "Lavender Health": Frank Oldham Jr., Project Coordinator at [Men of Color AIDS Prevention Services (MOCA)], interviews Craig Harris, of Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC), regarding HIV/AIDS in the black gay community.
    - Gay USA, Vol. [VIII], Episode No. 6 [Air date: 8/2/1990], August 1990; ID: 231.0102 (Box 7, Media ID: 231.0102)
    - Gay USA, Vol. [VIII], Episode No. 7 [Air date: 8/9/1990], August 1990; ID: 231.0103 (Box 7, Media ID: 231.0103)
      Duration: 3/4 in. Umatic
      TRT: 00:59:00
      1. Lou Maletta interviews Rick Panson, owner of Duplex bar, regarding the boycott of Miller beer.
      2. Lou Maletta interviews Dino Rossi, of ACTUP, regarding the boycott of Miller beer.
      3. Karen [Ocamb], of GCN Los Angeles, questions Reverend Louis Sheldon, Fundamentalist minister, regarding his tax-exempt status. Includes undercover footage.
      4. Karen [Ocamb] of GCN Los Angeles, interviews John Duran, Esq., Attorney at Law, regarding Reverend Louis Sheldon's tax-exempt status.
      5. Footage of "Pink Panthers On The Prowl" event. Includes interviews with Gerri Wells, Coordinator of the Pink Panthers; Red Mahoney, Chair Christopher Street Festival; Dale, of the Pink Panthers; Byron, of the Pink Panthers; [Allen] Contini, victim of bashing; [Ron Gruenwald] of ACTUP and Queer Nation; and Mike and Tina, 'Just visiting NYC'.
      COMMERCIAL: SF AIDS Foundation, "The Condom: Don't leave home without it"
      6. "All About Women": Rebecca Lewin interviews Marjorie Hill, NYC Mayor Dinkins' Liaison to the gay and lesbian community, regarding her position and responsibilities.
      7. Karen [Ocamb] interviews John Duran, Esq., Mr. Christopher St. West, regarding a neo-Nazi group in Orange County called White Aryan Resistance (WAR).
      8. "Naming Names": Karin Schwartz, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD), discusses the exclusion of gays and lesbians in a new promotion by American Express and Continental Airlines.
      9. "Lavender Health": Frank Oldham Jr., Project Coordinator for [Men of Color AIDS Prevention (MOCA)], interviews Eric Perez, Community Associate of the (MOCA) Project, regarding a recent study on black men concerning AIDS prevention.
      10. Footage of the Gay Games 1990 in Vancouver, British Columbia
    - [1]--Gay USA, Vol. [VIII], Episode No. 8 [Air date: 8/16/1990] [2]--Pride and Progress, August 1990; ID: 231.0104 (Box 7, Media ID: 231.0104)
    - Gay USA, Vol. [VIII], Episode No. 9 [Air date: 8/24/1990], August 1990; ID: 231.0105 (Box 7, Media ID: 231.0105)
    - Gay USA, Vol. [VIII], Episode No. 10 [Air date: 8/30/1990], August 1990; ID: 231.0106 (Box 7, Media ID: 231.0106)
    - Gay USA, Vol. [VIII], Episode No. 11 [Air date: 9/6/1990], September 1990; ID: 231.0107 (Box 7, Media ID: 231.0107)
    - Gay USA, Vol. [VIII], Episode No. 12 [Air date: 9/13/1990], September 1990; ID: 231.0108 (Box 7, Media ID: 231.0108)
    - Gay USA, Vol. [VIII], Episode No. 13 [Air date: 9/20/1990], September 1990; ID: 231.0109 (Box 7, Media ID: 231.0109)
      COMMERCIAL: 550-TOOL (8665), ONLY .15 MIN - .40 FIRST MIN
      1. Footage of victory party for Deborah Glick, Democratic nominee for NYS Assembly. Includes Andy Humm interviewing Deborah Glick regarding her political views.
      2. "All About Women": Rebecca Lewin interviews Sandra Rovira, surviving spouse of AT&T employee Marjorie Forlini, regarding her lawsuit against AT&T regarding her denial of surviving spouse benefits.
      3. Clip of music video "Blood Bath" by Phranc, lesbian music artist. Introduced by Brandon Judell.
      4. Nicholas Schaeffner, Philip-Morris stockholder, discusses his letter to Philip-Morris regarding his family's disapproval of the company's support of Senator Jesse Helms.
      5. "Lavender Health": Ron Vachon, Director of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns, interviews Marjorie Hill, PhD, Director of the NYC Mayor's Office for Lesbian and Gay Community, regarding the functions of her office.
      6. "Naming Names": Dr. Henry Yeager, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD), discusses a recent article in Ebony magazine titled "An Honest Look at Black Gays and Lesbians".
      7. Lou Maletta interviews Catherine Saalfield, Curator of the Lookout Lesbian and Gay Video Festival, regarding the festival. Includes clips of "Laws and Skin" by Chris Martin and "Degas of the B-Boys" by Matt Ebert.
      8. Barry Miller, of the Gay and Lesbian Switchboard, discusses the Fall Frolic Festival and Follies.
      9. Lou Maletta interviews [Matthew] Geller, Exhibit Curator of "From Receiver to Remote Control" at The New Museum of Contemporary Art.
      10. Lou Maletta encourages viewers to contact Richard Aurelio, President of Time Warner NYC, to give GCN more time to negotiate their contract.
      COMMERCIAL: Long Island Association for AIDS Care (LIAAC), for the second annual pledge walk
      11. Footage of Jack Hoffman in "Don't Tell Mama".
      COMMERCIAL: Brought to you in part by 550-TOOL (8665), ONLY .15 MIN - .40 FIRST MIN
    - Gay USA, Vol. [VIII], Episode No. 14 [Air date: 9/27/1990], September 1990; ID: 231.0110 (Box 7, Media ID: 231.0110)
      Currently not available for viewing
    - Gay USA, Vol. [VIII], Episode No. 15 [Air date: 10/4/1990], October 1990; ID: 231.0111 (Box 7, Media ID: 231.0111)
      1. Andy Humm discusses the demise of the Fund for Human Dignity.
      2. Interview: Ed Mickens, Former Consultant, discusses the demise of the Fund for Human Dignity.
      3. Lou Maletta discusses GCN's move to a different channel at a different time.
      4. "All About Women": Rebecca Lewin interviews Dell Richards, author, regarding her book "Lesbian Lists: A Look at Lesbian Culture, History, and Personalities".